Finding Aid for Vice-President for Development (University of Michigan) records, 1948-[ongoing]
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Development Office, 1943-1992
  - Photographs and Slides, 1950s-1980s
    - Slides, 1950s-1980s
      - University of Michigan
        - Individuals
          - M
            - May, Jerry (Box 37)
            - Mazrui, Ali (Box 37)
            - Mecouch, John (Box 37)
            - Mendler, Janet (Box 37)
            - Miller, Warren (Box 37)
            - Milliken, Governor William (Box 37)
            - Mirageas, Evans (Box 37)
            - Moody, Charles (Box 37)
            - Morris, Aldon (Box 37)
            - Morris, Barbara (Box 37)
            - Mueller, Eva (Box 37)
            - Muir, Roy (Box 37)
          - N
            - Nace, George (Box 37)
            - Nordby, Virginia (Box 37)
            - Nelson, Wilbur (Box 37)
            - Niehuss, Marvin (Box 37)
            - Nielsen, Neal (Box 37)
            - Norman, A.G (Box 37)
            - Norman, Jessye (Box 37)
            - Nugent, Anita (Box 37)
          - O
            - Oberdich, Will (Box 37)
            - Oswald, Marina (Box 37)
            - Owen, Robert (Box 37)
            - Owsley, Joe (Box 37)
            - Overseth, Anneke (Box 37)
          - Overberger, Charles (Box 37)
          - Power, Eugene (Box 37)
          - P
            - Packard, Jim (Box 37)
            - Palazzola, Guy (Box 37)
            - Parris, Joan (Box 37)
            - Patrick, William (Box 37)
            - Peacock, Wade (Box 37)
            - Peckham, Howard (Box 37)
            - Perry, Lowell (Box 37)
            - Phillips, Dick (Box 37)
            - Pierpont, W.K (Box 37)
            - Pointer Sisters (Box 37)
            - Polakowski, Ken (Box 37)
            - Pollack, James (Box 37)
            - Porter, John (Box 37)
            - Potter, Robert (Box 37)
            - Power, Sarah, Goddard (Box 37)
          - R
            - Radock, Michael (Box 37)
            - Reisman, Joan (Box 37)
            - Reister, Russell (Box 37)
            - Revelli, William (Box 37)
            - Reynolds, H. Robert (Box 37)
            - Reynolds, Richard (Box 37)
            - Roach, Thomas (Box 37)
            - Rusk, Dean (Box 37)
            - Ruthven, Alexander (Box 37)
          - Rickover, Hyman (Box 37)
          - S
            - Sain, Leonard (Box 37)
            - Selikoff, Irving (Box 37)
            - Schumacher, Hazen (Box 37)
            - Schwadron, Harley (Box 37)
            - Shortt, James (Box 37)
            - Simpson, Carole (Box 37)
            - Smith, Otis (Box 37)
            - Smith, Veronica (Box 37)
            - Snow, C. P (Box 37)
            - Snydey, Bloige (Box 37)
            - Standifer, James (Box 37)
            - Stegath, William (Box 37)
            - Steiner, Peter (Box 37)
            - Stewart, Mary J (Box 37)
            - Stirton, William (Box 37)
            - Sutton, Roger (Box 37)
          - Shapiro, Harold
            - General (Box 37)
            - (July 27) regents meeting--named president, 1979 (Box 37)
            - 1987--announces acceptance of Princeton presidency (Box 37)
          - Smith, Allan F. (interim president) (Box 37)
          - T
            - Townes, Henry K (Box 37)
          - V
            - Varner, Nellie (Box 37)
            - Vasse, William (Box 37)
          - W
            - Wallace, Mike (Box 37)
            - Warden, Eric (Box 37)
            - Wei, Julie (Box 37)
            - Wheeler, Albert (Box 37)
            - Wilder, Lawrence Douglas (Box 37)
            - Williams, G. Mennen (Box 37)
            - Wilson, Harold (Box 37)
            - Woods, Ronald (Box 37)
            - Worden, Alfred (Box 37)
            - Wyllie, Cleland (Box 37)
          - Y
            - Yoder, Sharon (Box 37)
            - Yost, Fielding (Box 37)
          - Miscellaneous (Box 37)
        - Research [slide box]
          - Anatomy lab--hearing clinic, 1960s (Box 37)
          - Computers, 1960s (Box 37)
          - Bioengineering, 1960s (Box 37)
          - Biological Sciences, 1980s (Box 37)
          - Body imager [Technologist at control panel of], 1968 (Box 37)
          - Comp and Electrical Engineering, 1980s (Box 37)
          - Cyclotron, 1960s (Box 37)
          - Electron physics laboratory, 1960s (Box 37)
          - Highway Safety Research Institute, 1960s-1970s (Box 37)
          - Laurentian research vessel--Africa, 1980s (Box 37)
          - Metallurgy, high temperature, 1960 (Box 37)
          - Naval Architecture, 1960s (Box 37)
          - Oceanic and Atmospheric Research, 1980s (Box 37)
          - Phoenix Atomic Research Laboratory/Ford Nuclear Reactor, 1960s; 1980s (Box 37)
          - Radioisotope laboratory, 1960s (Box 37)
          - Radio Telescope [with Soviet visitors], 1960s (Box 37)
          - Robotic welding system (Box 37)
          - Rocket firing, 1964 (Box 37)
          - Schisto--Africa, 1972 (Box 37)
          - Sub-Mich [submarine], 1967 (Box 37)
          - Surgery, 1960s (Box 37)
          - Television Center, 1967 (Box 37)
          - Water hammer, 1960s (Box 37)
          - Wind tunnel (Aerospace Engineering), 1960s (Box 37)
        - Student activities
          - General (Box 37)
          - All-Campus Orchestra concert, December 1982 (Box 37)
          - Art School tapestry project, 1976 (Box 37)
          - Football
            [See Slide Box in Box 38]
            - General, 1957-1986 (Box 37)
              (primarily 1960s)
              [crowds, cheerleaders, practice, stadium scenes]
            - Games
              - Michigan State, 1957 (Box 37)
              - Oregon State, 1959 (Box 37)
              - Illinois, 1964 (Box 37)
              - Rose Bowl, 1965 (Box 37)
              - Purdue, 1982 (Box 37)
              - Rose Bowl, 1983 (Box 37)
            - Individuals
              - Elliott, Bump (Box 37)
              - Mason, Tony (Box 37)
              - Revelli (Box 37)
          - Homecoming, 1961-1967; undated (Box 37)
          - Men's Glee Club (Box 37)
          - Michigamua, 1966 (Box 37)
          - Michigras, 1960; 1962; 1964 (Box 37)
          - Marching band [slide box], 1959-1969; 1976-1977; 1981-1982 (Box 38)
          - Protests and rallies (Box 38)
          - Registration, 1960s-1970s (Box 38)
          - Symphony, 1960s (Box 38)
          - Theater
            - "Runaways" (Box 38)
            - "A Troupe of Action" (Box 38)
            - University Theater Program (Box 38)
          - Women's Glee Club (Box 38)
        - Miscellaneous
          - Alumni Camp, 1963 (Box 38)
          - Computers (Box 38)
          - Dearborn campus [in slide box] (Box 38)
          - English Composition Board (Box 38)
          - Flint campus [in slide box] (Box 38)
          - Interlochen (Box 38)
          - Rackham Building--Detroit (Box 38)
            [in slide box]
      - Ann Arbor scenes
        [see also slide box]
        - Aerial views (Box 38)
        - Art Fair (Box 38)
        - Businesses (Box 38)
        - Ronald McDonald house (Box 38)
        - Street scenes (Box 38)
    - Photographs, 1976-1991
      - Blanchard, James, Campaign for Michigan (negatives), October 1983 (Box 48)
      - Commencement reception with Governor John Engler (negatives, contact sheets, photograph), May 4, 1991 (Box 48)
      - Donor Relations Museum of Art reception (negatives, contact sheets), October 19, 1990 (Box 48)
      - Football Brunch
        - (photographs), September 26, 1987 (Box 48)
        - (negatives, contact sheets, photographs), October 31, 1987 (Box 48)
        - (negatives, contact sheets, photographs), November 1, 1986 (Box 48)
      - Ford, Gerald 1976, undated (negative, photographs) (Box 48)
      - Hill Auditorium foyer (photograph), undated (Box 48)
      - Miscellaneous events and activities (slides), 1977-1987 (Box 48)
      - Miscellaneous individuals 1988-1989, undated (photographs) (Box 48)
      - Partners in Leadership receptions
        - Grand Rapids, MI (negatives, contact sheets), May 2, 1991 (Box 48)
        - Miscellaneous (negatives, contact sheets, photographs), 1989-1991 (Box 48)
  - Staff Files
    This group of records is comprised of the files of a number of staff members. The records were for the most part fragmentary and unorganized when they arrived at the Bentley Library.
    - Annual Funds Coordinating Council, 1969-1986
      The Annual Funds Coordinating Council was established to coordinate the fundraising activities of schools, colleges, and other units and to assist the development officers of these units in improving their professional skills. This series (2.3 linear feet) dates from 1969 to 1986. Bulking largest in this series are meeting minutes and samples of fundraising appeals disseminated by the units.
      - History (Box 24)
      - Alumni Association, 1979/80-1983/84 (Box 24)
      - Capital Campaign Advisory Committee, 1984 (Box 24)
      - Coordinated Calendar
        - 1976/77, 1978/79-1980/81 (Box 24)
        - 1981/82-1984/85 (Box 24)
      - Correspondence, 1982-1984 (Box 24)
      - Deans Club
        - 1977 (Box 24)
          [Ad Hoc Committee to Study Deans Club Concept]
        - 1978, 1984 (Box 24)
      - Donor Publication Survey, 1978 (Box 24)
      - Executive Committee, 1985 (Box 24)
      - Faculty Programs, 1979 (Box 24)
      - General information, 1977-1981 (Box 24)
        [degree overlap; funds received by schools and colleges]
      - Goodwin, Bill, 1977-1979 (Box 24)
        [notes, plans]
      - Guidelines
        - Guidelines on Fundraising Activities, 1969 (Box 24)
        - Guidelines for Capital Campaigns at the University of Michigan, 1974 (Box 24)
        - Annual and Special Funds Coordinating Guidelines, 1976 (Box 24)
      - Meetings
        - 1974 (Box 24)
        - 1975/76
          - Complete minutes (Box 24)
          - Summary minutes (Box 24)
        - 1976/77
          - Complete minutes (Box 24)
          - Summary minutes (Box 24)
        - 1977/78 (Box 24)
        - 1978/79 (Box 24)
        - 1979/80, 10 folders (Box 24)
        - 1980/81, 10 folders (Box 24)
        - 1981/82, 10 folders (Box 24)
        - 1982/83, 10 folders (Box 24)
        - 1983/84, 10 folders (Box 24)
        - 1984/85 (Box 25)
      - Membership lists, 1979-1985 (Box 25)
      - Memoranda
        - 1975-1976 (Box 25)
        - 1977-1978 (Box 25)
        - 1985-1986, 2 folders (Box 25)
      - Memorial gifts, 1976-1977 (Box 25)
      - Phonathon, 1982-1985 (Box 25)
        [central phonathon center proposal]
      - Planning Committee, 1984/85 (Box 25)
      - Premiums Policy, 1979-1981 (Box 25)
      - Schools and Colleges
        - General
          - Degree overlap, 1979-1984 (scattered) (Box 25)
          - Monthly reports, 1979/80 (Box 25)
          - Samples of fundraising appeals, 1975/76-1979/80; 5 folders (Box 25)
          - Samples of gift acknowledgment, 1980-1981 (Box 25)
          - Services to schools and colleges, 1981 (Box 25)
        - Architecture, 1981/82-1984/85 (Box 25)
        - Art, 1979/80-1981/82 (Box 25)
        - Athletic Department, 1979/80 (Box 25)
        - Business Administration, 1978/79-1983/84 (Box 25)
        - Dearborn, 1979/80-1983/84 (Box 25)
        - Dentistry, 1979/80-1982/83 (Box 25)
        - Education, 1976/77-1983/84 (Box 25)
        - Engineering, 1979/80-1983/84 (Box 25)
        - Flint, 1979/80-1984/85 (Box 25)
        - Hospitals, 1979/80-1983/84 (Box 25)
        - Law School, 1977/78-1983/84 (Box 25)
        - Library Science, 1976/77-1983/84 (Box 25)
        - Literature, Science, and the Arts, 1977/78-1982/83 (Box 25)
        - Medical School, 1978/79-1981/82 (Box 26)
        - Music, 1979/80; 1983/84 (Box 26)
        - Natural Resources, 1978/79-1984/85 (Box 26)
        - Nursing, 1979/80 (Box 26)
        - Pharmacy, 1974/75; 1979/80-1983/84 (Box 26)
        - Public Health, 1974/75-1983/84 (scattered) (Box 26)
        - Rackham, 1971/72-1981/82 (scattered) (Box 26)
        - Social Work, 1970/71-1982/83 (scattered) (Box 26)
      - Special Study Committee on School and College Fundraising, 1969-1972 (Box 26)
      - Student Programs
        - Foreign students, 1979/80 (Box 26)
        - Pledge programs, 1980 (Box 26)
        - Rowing Club, 1980 (Box 26)
        - Student relationships with Development, 1979/80 (Box 26)
        - WCBN fundraisers, 1980-1981 (Box 26)
      - WUOM, 1981/82-1983/84 (Box 26)
    - Annual Giving Program, 1970-1989
      The Annual Giving Program series (2.5 linear feet), dating from 1970 to 1989, likewise contains samples of mail solicitations (see "Direct Mail"), as well as meeting materials and proposals for various fundraising programs. For information on the evolution and overall functioning of the Development Office in the 1980s, and in particular the annual giving program, researchers should see the folders "Background material for new staff" and "Overview of fundraising at the University of Michigan" as well as the Implementation Committee meetings and report.
      - Activity reports (staff), 1983-1985 (Box 26)
      - Background material for new staff, 1989; 3 folders (Box 26)
      - Budget
        - 1983/84 (Box 26)
        - 1984/85 (Box 26)
      - Consulting
        - Dentistry, School of, 1983 (Box 26)
        - Flint, University of Michigan, 1983 (Box 26)
        - Gerontology, 1982 (Box 26)
        - Natural Resources, School of, 1982/83 (Box 26)
        - Martin Luther Quincentennial, 1982 (Box 26)
        - WUOM (Box 26)
      - Defense of Annual Giving, 1984 (Box 26)
      - Direct Mail
        - Analysis
          - 1970-1979 (Box 26)
          - 1980-1981 (Box 26)
          - 1981-1982 (Box 26)
          - 1982-1983 (Box 26)
          - 1983-1984 (Box 26)
        - Mail solicitation samples
          - 1971, 3 folders (Box 26)
          - 1972, 3 folders (Box 26)
          - 1973-1985, 13 folders (Box 27)
      - Goal Setting for the Eighties, 1982 (Box 27)
      - Homecoming, 1983 (Box 27)
      - Implementation Committee
        - Meetings, 1984-1985 (Box 27)
        - Report, 1985 (Box 27)
      - Interim plans, 1985 (Box 27)
      - Kasdan, Lawrence: film equipment fund, 1983-1984 (Box 27)
      - Management Review, 1983 (Box 27)
      - Michigan Annual Giving Committee
        - General, 1984-1985 (Box 27)
        - Meetings
          - 1982 (Box 27)
          - 1983 (Box 27)
          - June 8-9, 1984 (Box 27)
          - October 12-13, 1984 (Box 27)
        - Membership lists, 1973-1984 (Box 27)
        - Nominating Committee, 1984 (Box 27)
        - Student Aid Program Study Group, 1982 (Box 27)
        - Student aid proposal
          - General, 1982-1984; 2 folders (Box 27)
          - Background material (Box 27)
          - Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 27)
          - Preketes, Alice, files (Box 27)
      - Overview of fundraising at the University of Michigan, 1982 (Box 27)
      - Peacock, Wade, files, 1983-1985 (Box 28)
      - Phonathons
        - General, 1981-1987 (Box 28)
        - Dow Chemical Company, 1980-1982 (Box 28)
        - General Electric, 1981-1982 (Box 28)
        - Planning a Phonathon--A Workbook (Box 28)
        - Training Session, 1983 (Box 28)
      - Plan [for Annual Giving Programs Office], 1988 (Box 28)
      - Policies and practices, 1984 (Box 28)
      - Projection of activities, January-June 1983 (Box 28)
      - Reports--Gifts, 1982/83; 1984/85 (Box 28)
      - Sailing team fundraising proposal, 1980/81 (Box 28)
      - Staff, 1983/84 (Box 28)
      - Statistics, 1984 (Box 28)
      - Student Awareness Program
        - General, 1980-1982 (Box 28)
        - Proposals, 1981-1983 (Box 28)
      - Student Awareness Study Committee, 1981; 2 folders (Box 28)
      - Task Force on Annual Giving Programs, 1983-1984 (Box 28)
      - Telephone solicitation proposals, 1976 (Box 28)
      - Vital Margin Fund, 1977-1984 (scattered) (Box 28)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 28)
    - Capital Campaigns, 1978-1988
      Capital Campaigns (.75 linear feet) dates from 1978 to 1988 and consists primarily of material relating to the Campaign for Michigan undertaken in 1983, along with a development plan for the eighties and more general material on capital campaigns.
      - Campaign for Michigan, 1983-1987
        - All-Alumni Solicitation, 1983-1985; 2 folders (Box 28)
        - Brochures
          - General (Box 28)
          - Alumni Center (Box 28)
          - Eye Center (Box 28)
          - Replacement Hospital Project (Box 28)
        - Campaign Briefing, 1983-1985 (Box 28)
          [many issues missing]
        - Case statement (Box 28)
        - Committee on Resources (Medical)
          - 1982, 2 folders (Box 28)
          - 1983 (Box 29)
        - Debrodt, Robert--correspondence, 1982 (Box 29)
        - Goals, 1981-1982 (Box 29)
        - Plans, 1983 (Box 29)
        - Prospect coordination policy, 1983 (Box 29)
        - Prospects (Box 29)
        - Retreat (Box 29)
        - Special gifts (Box 29)
        - Telefund Final Report, 1988 (Box 29)
        - Volunteer organization chart (Box 29)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 29)
      - Capital funding needs, 1978 (Box 29)
      - Development Plan for the Eighties, 1981 (Box 29)
      - Guidelines (Box 29)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 29)
    - Cultural Programs, 1970-1984
      Cultural Programs/Friends Groups (.8 linear feet) dates from 1970 to 1984. This series contains minutes of meetings of the Cultural Fundraising Group and material documenting the fundraising efforts of units such as the Museum of Art and the Clements Library. Information on various friends groups is included. This series is fragmentary and uneven.
      - General (Box 29)
      - Bentley Historical Library, 1972-1982 (Box 29)
      - Clements Library
        - 1970-1982 (scattered) (Box 29)
        - 1783 Conference, 1982 (Box 29)
      - Cultural Fundraising Group meetings, 1979-1982; 15 folders (Box 29)
      - Friends Groups--miscellaneous (Box 29)
      - Friends of Dance, 1979-1983 (Box 29)
      - Kelsey Museum, 1977-1982; 2 folders (Box 29)
      - Matthaei Botanical Gardens, 1979 (Box 29)
      - Michigan Ensemble Theatre, 1979-1982 (Box 29)
      - Museum of Art
        - Art and Antique Auction, 1980-1983 (Box 29)
        - Correspondence, 1979-1982 (Box 29)
        - Council of the Friends, 1979-1983; 2 folders (Box 29)
        - Friends Committee, 1979-1983; 2 folders (Box 30)
      - Stearns Collection, 1978-1981 (Box 30)
      - University Musical Society, 1979-1984 (Box 30)
    - Development Council, 1963-1985
      Development Council (.5 linear feet), dating from 1963-1985, is a small series consisting of supporting materials for board of directors meetings; charters and bylaws; correspondence of Thomas Koykka; and background information for the Special Study Committee on School and College Fundraising, also known as the Slykhouse committee. The bulk of the Development Council records are contained in a separate record group, the University of Michigan Development Council.
      - Board of Directors meeting materials
        - 1973/74 (Box 30)
        - 1975/76-1976/77, 2 folders (Box 30)
        - 1978/79-1981/82, 4 folders (Box 30)
        - 1984/85 (Box 30)
      - Charter of organization and bylaws, 1963-1982 (scattered) (Box 30)
      - Correspondence: Thomas V. Koykka, 1976-1984; 2 folders (Box 30)
      - Slykhouse committee: background material (Box 30)
    - Tappan Hall Fundraising, 1977-1985
      Tappan Hall Fundraising (.7 linear feet) dates from 1977 to 1985 and documents the campaign to raise funds to renovate Tappan Hall, the art history building.
      - Brochure (draft), 1982-1983 (Box 30)
      - Buffet supper, September 1982 (Box 30)
      - Campaign plan, 1982 (Box 30)
      - Corporate prospects, 1982; 1984 (Box 30)
      - Correspondence, 1977-1983 (Box 30)
      - Dedication of Tappan Hall, November 15, 1985 (Box 30)
      - Foundation prospects
        - General, 1982-1983 (Box 30)
        - Helen Clay Frick Foundation, 1982 (Box 30)
        - Japan Foundation, 1982 (Box 30)
        - JEC Fund (Expo), 1982-1984 (Box 30)
        - Kress Foundation, 1979-1982 (Box 31)
        - Kresge Foundation, 1980-1983 (Box 31)
        - Metropolitan Center for Far Eastern Art Studies, 1982-1984 (Box 31)
      - Freeman, Henry B., 1983 (Box 31)
      - Sasaki, Kozo, 1982-1984 (Box 31)
      - Shapiro, Vivian, 1983 (Box 31)
      - Solicitation of faculty and graduates, 1983 (Box 31)
      - Steering Committee for the Revitalization of Tappan Hall, 1982 (Box 31)
    - Topical File, 1979-1992
      The Topical File (1.75 linear feet), dating from 1970 to 1984, 1989, and 1991/92 consists of miscellaneous files documenting the activities of the Development Office, arranged alphabetically. Of special note are the development handbook in box 32, which provides a description of the University's development program in the early 1970s, and the Development Education Program orientation notebook, which provides a similar overview of the development program in the year 1991/92. To assist the researcher in understanding the complex and ever-shifting structure of the Development Office, a complete set of organization charts for the years 1971 to 1990 has been placed in the Topical File.
      - Alumni Development Data Base [Alumni Development Information System], 1972-1977; 2 folders (Box 31)
      - Alumni gifts to Michigan since the organization of the Development Council in, 1953; 1970-1983 (Box 31)
      - Alumni Report, December 1984 (Box 31)
        [alumni/donor statistics]
      - Awards and scholarships
        - Breakthrough Scholarship Project (Disabled Student Services), 1982-1983 (Box 31)
        - McGreaham-Siwik Scholarship, 1982-1983 (Box 31)
        - Kelsey-Lynch Award, 1982 (Box 31)
        - Miller, Arthur, Award, 1982 (Box 31)
      - Benefactors, 1974/75-1980/81 (Box 31)
      - Big Ten Development Officers
        - Conferences, 1983; 1984 (Box 31)
        - Directories, 1982; 1983 (Box 31)
      - Brochures--correspondence re, 1981-1983 (Box 31)
      - Council for Advancement and Support of Education (CASE) awards
        - Awards won by the University of Michigan (1964-1984) (Box 31)
        - Conferences, 1975-1978 (Box 31)
        - Entries
          - 1972 (Box 31)
          - 1975
            - Major Gifts (Box 31)
            - Presidents Club (Box 31)
          - 1976-1982, 7 folders (Box 31)
          - 1983
            - General (Box 31)
            - Alumni Incentive Awards (Box 31)
            - Direct Mail: Student Involvement Programs (Box 31)
          - 1984 (Box 31)
            [includes photographs]
          - 1989 (Box 31)
      - Consulting
        - Dickinson, Joseph E., 1972-1973; 2 folders (Box 31)
        - Goebel, Paul [Grand Rapids office], 1969; 1971-1981; 2 folders (Box 31)
      - Council for Financial Aid to Education (CFAE): percentage of alumni participation in annual giving, 1972-1984 (scattered) (Box 32)
      - Council of Michigan Foundations, 1973-1976 (Box 32)
      - Deans Club
        - General, 1980-1985 (Box 32)
        - Monthly reports, 1984/85 (Box 32)
      - Deferred Giving (Box 32)
      - Development Education Program: Orientation Notebook, 1991/92 (Box 32)
      - Development Handbook
        [a description of the University of Michigan development program]
        - 1972 (Box 32)
        - 1972 with, 1973 revisions (Box 32)
      - Development Goals, A Formula for Projecting, 1980 (Box 32)
      - Development Office staff files
        - Activity reports, 1974-1982 (Box 32)
          (scattered)
        - Correspondence, 1979; 1983 (Box 32)
        - Management Review and Audit, 1982 (Box 32)
        - Memoranda, 1979-1982 (Box 32)
        - President's reports (annual reports--drafts), 1981/82; 1982/83 (Box 32)
        - Program evaluation, 1975 (Box 32)